so in this video we're going to look at
所以在这个视频中，我们将要看
arrows theorem and prove it formally so
箭头定理并正式证明它
to begin let's establish the notation
首先让我们建立符号
that we'll use throughout this video
我们将在整个视频中使用
I'll let n be the set of agents I'll let
我将让n为代理
L be a finite set of outcomes so these
我是有限的一组结果
are the candidates that the agents are
是代理商的候选人
going to have preferences over and the
将有偏好，并且
really important thing about o is going
关于o真正重要的事情是
to be that there are at least three
至少有三个
candidates so arrows theorem is going to
候选人，所以箭头定理将
require that we have at least three
要求我们至少有三个
candidates that we're voting over I'm
我们正在投票的候选人
going to use I all to denote the set of
我将用所有这些来表示
all possible strict preference orderings
所有可能的严格优先顺序
over o so I'm going to be speaking here
结束了，所以我要在这里讲话
only about strict orderings that means
仅关于严格的订购意味着
that agents don't have any ties in their
代理商没有任何联系
preferences in the end arrows theorem is
最终箭头定理中的首选项为
going to end up telling us that any
最终会告诉我们
desirable social welfare function can't
理想的社会福利功能不能
exist even if preferences are restricted
即使偏好受到限制也存在
to be strict so this restriction to
严格来说，这样限制
strictness is not going to be a limiting
严格性不会成为限制
thing it's actually going to be a
事情实际上将是
strengthening thing we're gonna end up
我们要加强的事情
seeing that we can't have good social
看到我们不能拥有良好的社交
welfare functions even if preferences
福利功能，即使偏好
are strict I'm going to use this
严格，我要用这个
notation here to denote an element of
此处的符号表示
the set L to the N so in other words
将L设置为N，换句话说
this is going to be a preference profile
这将是一个偏好设置
a preference ordering one for every
优先订购一个
agent and this is of course the input
代理，这当然是输入
that our social welfare function takes
我们的社会福利职能
so recall that a social welfare function
所以回想一下，社会福利功能
is a mapping from a preference profile a
是偏好配置文件a的映射
set of preferences one for every agent
一组偏好为每个代理
to a single preference ordering which is
到单个首选项排序是
the social welfare ordering going on
进行社会福利命令
I'll denote with this symbol a
我用这个符号表示
preference an ordering relation here
偏好这里的订购关系
subscripted by a W the preference
W优先选择
ordering that is actually output by the
实际输出的命令
social welfare function so as I just
社会福利功能
said the social welfare function itself
说社会福利功能本身
outputs an ordering and this is going to
输出命令，这将
be the ordering baguettes
是订购法式长棍面包
put and now when the input to W is
放，现在当W的输入是
ambiguous I might actually have even
我可能实际上甚至有歧义
more complicated notation here saying
更复杂的符号在这里说
precisely which ordering it is so so in
确切地说是这样的顺序
particular this notation here is going
特别是这种符号在这里
to mean the preference order in output
表示输出中的优先顺序
by W when given the preference profile
给定偏好配置文件时，按W
here as input and I'm going to care
这里作为输入，我要照顾
about this in particular when I sort of
尤其是当我
change around which preference ordering
更改首选项顺序
it is that I talk about okay so now let
是我谈论好的，所以现在让
me formally state the conditions that
我正式陈述条件
arrows theorem speaks about the first is
箭头定理讲的第一个是
purrito efficiency so recall the idea of
Purrito效率，所以回想一下
pre to efficiency is that when everybody
效率的前提是当每个人
agrees on how to outcomes should be
同意如何取得成果
ranked if it's the case that every agent
如果是每个代理商，则进行排名
thinks that a is better than B then the
认为a比B好，然后
social welfare function is required also
还需要社会福利功能
to output that a is better than B and
输出a优于B并且
this is only the case when everybody is
只有当每个人都
unanimous if even one person feels
即使一个人都感到一致
differently this doesn't restrict us at
不同的是，这并不限制我们
all so formally I'll say that a social
这么正式地说，我会说
welfare function W is purrito efficient
福利函数W是purrito有效的
if for any pair of outcomes
如果有任何一对结果
o 1 and O 2 from the set of outcomes if
如果结果集中为o 1和O 2
it's the case that for all agents I
对于所有代理商来说，
outcome 1 is preferred to outcome 2 then
结果1比结果2优先
it must be that the social welfare
一定是社会福利
function also chooses a 1 preferred to O
函数还选择了1而不是O
2 so the next definition we need to set
2所以我们需要设置下一个定义
up arrows impossibility theorem is the
向上箭头不可能定理是
idea of independence of irrelevant
不相关的独立思想
alternatives so intuitively the idea
替代品如此直观
here is that we want to say that the
这是我们要说的
social welfare function should decide
社会福利职能应决定
the ordering between two outcomes a and
两个结果a和之间的排序
B based only on the relative rankings
B仅基于相对排名
that all of the agents give to these two
所有的特工都给这两个
outcomes so it should only be allowed to
结果，因此只应允许
look at whether or not each individual
看每个人是否
agent puts a above or below B in order
代理商将B放在上方或下方
to decide whether a should go above or
决定a是否应高于或
below be in the final ranking and this
以下是最终排名，
should be true for every pair of
对于每对
outcomes so let's look at how we say
结果，让我们看看我们怎么说
this formally
正式地
we'll say that a social welfare function
我们说一个社会福利功能
W is independent of irrelevant
W独立于无关
alternatives if for any pair of outcomes
如果有任何一对结果的替代方案
o 1 and O 2 and any pair of perfect
o 1和O 2以及任何一对完美
profiles are called them pref Prime and
配置文件称为pref Prime和
pref double Prime the following
pref double Prime以下
condition is true so let's look at what
条件是真实的，所以让我们看一下
this condition here says this says o 1
这种情况在这里说这说o 1
is preferred by agent I improv prime 202
被代理商I即兴推荐202
if and only if o one is preferred by age
当且仅当o年龄优先
and I in pref double prime toe - so in
我穿着双头趾趾-所以在
other words this is saying when I
换句话说这就是当我
extended out the for all I here
扩展了我在这里的一切
this is saying that all of the agents
就是说所有代理商
relatively rank oh I wanna know - in the
相对排名哦，我想知道-在
same way in both pref Prime and pref
pref Prime和pref中的方法相同
double Prime in other words if agent I
换句话说，如果代理人I是双重素数
like so - better than o1 in pref Prime
像这样-在pref Prime中胜过o1
it must also be that agent I like so -
也一定是我喜欢的那个经纪人-
better than a1 in pref double Prime so
在首选双素中优于a1，因此
the condition says that if this is true
条件说如果这是真的
then it must be that the social welfare
那一定是社会福利
function when given prime as an input
给定素数作为输入时的功能
makes the same relative ranking between
使之间的相对排名相同
o 1 and O 2 as it does when given
给定时的o 1和O 2
preference and input so again in words
偏好并再次用文字输入
what we're saying here is that the
我们在这里所说的是
social welfare functions decision
社会福利职能决策
between oh one and O 2 in these two
在这两个中的一个和O 2之间
different preference profiles has to be
必须设置不同的首选项配置文件
the same if the relative ranking that
如果相对排名相同
all the agents make between these two
所有的代理商在这两个之间
things is also the same in both of these
这两件事也都一样
two orderings finally I'll define non
最后我要定义两个顺序
dictatorship as follows I'll say that a
独裁政权如下：
social welfare function does not have a
社会福利职能没有
dictator if there does not exist some
独裁者是否不存在
age at I for whom the following property
我的年龄，以下财产
is true for all outcomes
所有结果都是正确的
o 1 and O 2 it's the case that if agent
o 1和O 2是代理
I likes a one better than o - then it
我喜欢一个比o好-然后
must be that the
一定是
the welfare function also like so one
福利功能也像这样
better than o2 so in other words a
比o2好，换句话说a
dictator is somebody who simply
独裁者是一个简单地
determines the social welfare function
决定社会福利功能
it's the social welfare function if if
这是社会福利功能
it has a dictator is a function that
它有一个独裁者是一个功能
just listens only to one of its inputs
只听其输入之一
ignores the Preferences of everybody
忽略每个人的偏好
else and simply spits out the one
否则，简单地吐出一个
preference ordering that that comes from
来自的优先顺序
the one dictatorial agent okay having
一个独裁者可以
said all of these definitions were now
说所有这些定义现在
ready to formally define arrows theorem
准备正式定义箭头定理
so what we can say is any social welfare
所以我们可以说是任何社会福利
function W that is purrito efficient and
函数w是有效的
independent of irrelevant alternatives
独立于无关的选择
is dictatorial the way the proof works
证明工作的方式是独裁的
is as follows so so for the rest of this
如下所示，因此对于其余部分
video I'm going to give you the proof of
视频我要给你证明
this theorem which i think is a really
我认为这个定理真的
beautiful proof because we're able here
美丽的证明，因为我们能够在这里
to say something about a space of
说一些关于
functions space of very complicated
功能空间非常复杂
functions from sets of orderings into
从命令集到
orderings without knowing really what
不知道到底是什么
function we're talking about we want to
我们正在谈论的功能
assume simply that our function is PE
简单地假设我们的功能是PE
and III is pretty efficient and
III非常有效
independent of irrelevant alternatives
独立于无关的选择
and and we'll see that that assumption
而且我们将看到那个假设
is enough to show that it must be there
足以表明它必须在那里
tutorial now to avoid sweeping this
现在开始学习本教程，以避免扫除
under the rug let me again remind you
在地毯下让我再次提醒你
that we've made the assumption that the
我们已经假设
the number of outcomes is at least 3
结果数至少为3
that's important for this proof in a
这对于证明这一点很重要
sense really it's important because
感觉真的很重要，因为
independence of irrelevant alternatives
不相关选择的独立性
doesn't really mean anything in the case
在这种情况下并不意味着什么
of only two agents there could be in a
只有两个特工
relevant alternative if there are only
如果只有
two things to be compared so we're going
有两件事需要比较，所以我们要
to need to make use of the fact that
需要利用以下事实
there are at least three outcomes as
至少有三个结果
you'll see in the proof so let's get
您会在证明中看到，所以让我们
started so we're gonna proceed in four
开始，所以我们要在四个
steps we're gonna end up proving for
我们将要证明的步骤
intermediate claims which will
中间要求
eventually get us to the proof that this
最终使我们得到证明
social welfare function which we assume
我们假设的社会福利功能
is both free to efficient and
既免费又高效
independent of irrelevant alternatives
独立于无关的选择
must also be dictatorial so first of all
还必须是独裁的，所以首先
here's what I want to claim sounds like
这就是我想要声明的声音
a strange thing
一件奇怪的事
claim but it'll get us where we want to
声称，但是它将带我们到达我们想要的地方
go if every voter ranks some outcome be
如果每个选民的投票结果都不错，那就去吧
either at the very top of his
要么在他的最顶端
preferences or at the very bottom of his
偏好或他的最底层
preferences then it must be that the
则必须是
social welfare function also puts be
社会福利功能也将
either at the very top or the very
无论是在最顶端还是最顶端
bottom so let me draw kind of a picture
底部，让我画一幅画
of this so think of these as being a
因此，请认为这些是
bunch of preferences from all the
来自所有的一堆偏好
different agents and what I'm saying
不同的代理人和我在说什么
here is that each agent has to put me
这是每个特工都必须放我
either at the top or the bottom it
在顶部还是底部
doesn't matter which but they have to
没关系，但是他们必须
put it either at the top or at the
将其放在顶部或顶部
bottom and what I want to claim is that
底部，我想声称的是
the social welfare function then has to
然后，社会福利职能必须
do the same thing it either has to go
做同样的事情，要么必须去
here at the top or it have to go here at
在顶部，否则必须在这里
the bottom so let's see why that would
底部，让我们看看为什么会这样
be true so the way we're gonna do this
是真的，所以我们要做的方式
is will consider some arbitrary
是会考虑一些任意的
preference profile that satisfies this
满足此条件的偏好配置文件
condition every voter rank puts be
每个选民等级的条件是
either at the very top or the very
无论是在最顶端还是最顶端
bottom of their preferences and let's
他们的偏好的底部，让我们
assume for contradiction that the claim
认为索赔是矛盾的
that we've just made is not true instead
我们刚才所做的不是真的
that that we don't have be here but
我们没有在这里，但是
we've got it somewhere in the middle
我们把它放在中间
well in that case there must be some a
那么在那种情况下一定有一些
and some C where a is higher up in the
还有一些C在其中a更高
ordering for the social welfare function
订购社会福利功能
and C is lower down in the ordering
C在排序中较低
that's what it means to be in the middle
那就是中间的意思
there has to be something above it and
上面必须有东西
it has to be something below it so let's
它必须是低于它的东西，所以让我们
call those things a and C well now let's
现在将这些称为a和C，让我们
modify our ordering so that every voter
修改我们的顺序，以便每个选民
moves C just above a and his preference
将C移到a之上，并且他的偏好
ranking so so all of these rankings we
排名，所以所有这些排名
haven't drawn it but we have season A's
还没画，但是我们有第A季
in here somewhere because everybody is
因为每个人都在这里
ranking all of the different order all
排列所有不同的顺序
of the different outcomes in there
那里的不同结果
orderings so let's modify whatever this
订单，所以让我们修改一下
ranking is by by constraining where C
排名是通过约束C
and a go so let's imagine that
然后去吧，让我们想象一下
was in all of these different places and
在所有这些不同的地方
so on let's just move it so wherever si
所以就让它移动到任何地方
was before let's just stick it right
之前我们只是坚持正确
above a in the order in and leave
在顺序上方离开
everything else unchanged and let's call
其他一切保持不变，让我们打电话
that new preference whoops it's called a
这个新的喜好声叫它
new ranking pref Prime so so now we're
新排名优先Prime，所以现在我们
going to start using these definitions
将开始使用这些定义
that we've assumed about the preference
我们假设的偏好
ordering so we know from independence of
订购，因此我们从
irrelevant alternatives that in order
不相关的替代品
for this to change or for this to change
为了这个改变或改变
these two facts which we've assumed are
我们假设的两个事实是
true here the pairwise relationship
在这里是成对的关系
between a and B and or the pairwise
在a和B和或成对之间
relationship between B and C would have
B和C之间的关系
to change for some of the agents here
换一些代理商
however notice that B occupies an
但是请注意，B占据了一个
extremal position for all of the voters
所有选民的极端立场
and that means that C can be moved above
这意味着C可以移到上方
a moving from pref to Prime without
从偏好转换为素数而没有
changing any of the pairwise
改变成对的
relationships between C and B between a
C和B之间的关系
and b and thus we can conclude that in
和b，因此我们可以得出结论，
the preference profile
偏好设定档
Prof prime it's also the case that these
教授总理，这些情况也是如此
two things are true right we assume that
有两件事是对的，我们假设
those two things are true in pref for
这两件事在预言中是正确的
contradiction and and because nothing
矛盾，并且因为没有
has changed we can use iia to say that
已经改变了，我们可以用iia来表示
they must also be true and press run and
他们还必须是真实的，然后按运行
from transitivity we can just that the
从传递性中我们可以
fact that we were getting a strict
我们越来越严格的事实
ordering here we can also conclude
在这里订购我们还可以得出结论
therefore that that a must be ranked
因此，必须对a进行排名
above C in the social welfare function
社会福利功能中C以上
however look at the ordering that we've
但是看看我们的顺序
actually made here no recall that we put
实际上在这里没有使我们想起
C above a in every agents preference or
每个代理商偏好中C高于a或
wherever a was we stuck C just above
无论我们在哪里C都在上面
right well recall that preeto efficiency
很好，回想起效率
says that anytime all of the agents feel
说，任何时候所有代理商都觉得
exactly the same way about something the
完全相同的方式
social welfare function has to also feel
社会福利功能也必须
that way here all of the agents think
这样所有代理商都认为
that C is better than a
C比a好
so purrito efficiency requires that we
因此，purrito效率要求我们
would have see above a here but in fact
本来会在上面看到，但实际上
we have the opposite than a is above c
我们与c上方的a相反
so that gives us a contradiction so so
这样就给我们带来了矛盾
what does this all tell us it what we've
这一切告诉我们什么
established is what we have up here that
确定的是我们在这里拥有的
if every voter has some outcome B and an
如果每个选民都有一些结果B和一个
extremal point in his preference list it
在他的偏爱点上列出了它
must be that it goes into an extremal
一定是它进入了极端
point of the social welfare function as
社会福利功能的观点
well well so far that sounds fine it
到目前为止听起来还不错
doesn't seem like that gets us into big
似乎并没有使我们变得强大
trouble let's let's keep going and see
麻烦让我们继续前进，看看
what happens
怎么了
this is the the crucial step now so now
这是至关重要的一步，所以现在
I want to claim that there exists some
我想声称存在一些
special voter and I'm gonna give that
特别选民，我要给那个
voter a name I'm gonna call him n star
选民的名字，我叫他n星
who is extremely pivotal in the
谁在
following sense I want to say that he's
有一种感觉，我想说他是
able to change his vote at some
能够在某些地方改变他的投票
preference profile so there exists the
偏好设定档，因此存在
preference profile where if he changes
偏好配置文件，如果他改变了
his vote he can move a given outcome B
他的投票他可以移动给定的结果B
from being at the very bottom of the
从位于最底部
social ranking to the very top so there
社会排名最高
exists at least some circumstance in
存在至少某种情况
which some person is able to make a
某人能够做出的
really big difference to the social
对社会来说确实有很大的不同
choice he can move B from being the very
选择他可以将B从
least preferred thing to the very most
最不喜欢的东西
preferred thing let's see why that would
首选的东西，让我们看看为什么会这样
be true
是真实的
well let's consider a preference profile
好，让我们考虑一下偏好设置
pref in which every voter ranks B last
首选，每个选民都将B排在最后
and in which the voters preferences are
而选民的偏好是
otherwise completely unconstrained by
否则完全不受
preeto efficiency it must be the W also
效率必须是W
rates B length last because every
率B的长度持续，因为
pairwise relationship between B and
B和之间的成对关系
something else has that something else
其他还有其他
being preferred to B and so B has to be
比B更好，所以B必须是
at the very bottom of the social ranking
在社会排名的最底层
so now I want to basically let voters so
所以现在我想基本上让选民
I have some ordering over the voters
我对选民有一些命令
from 1 to N and I'm going to let them
从1到N，我要让他们
successively modify so let me gonna draw
连续修改，让我来画画
this so I've got all of these different
所以我有所有这些不同
rankings here from different voters and
来自不同选民的排名，以及
I've got some social welfare ranking
我有一些社会福利排名
here so we start out with everything at
在这里，所以我们从一切开始
the bottom and we
底部，我们
conclude from PE that B must be at the
从PE得出结论，B必须在
bottom here - so then I say let me one
在这里-那么我说让我一个
at a time
一次
take a voter and take B off being at the
带一名选民，让B离开
bottom and put it up at the top and let
底部并放在顶部，让
me see what happens when I do this
我看看当我这样做时会发生什么
there has to eventually be a change it
最终必须有所改变
can't be that I do this for everybody
不可能是我为所有人做到这一点
and B never changes because once I've
B永远不会改变，因为一旦我
done it absolutely for everybody and
绝对为每个人做到了
I've got B at the top all the way then
然后我一直把B放在最前面
pre to efficiency again is gonna
再次提高效率
constrain me and it's gonna say B has to
约束我，这会说B必须
be at the top so I know there has to be
在顶部，所以我知道必须有
somebody who in making these movements
做出这些动作的人
causes something to change at some point
在某些时候导致某些变化
so I'm gonna give the name and star to
所以我要给它起个名字和星号
the first voter in this apparently
这个第一选民显然
arbitrary ordering on the voters that
对选民的任意命令
I've got here whose change causes
我来这里是谁的变化原因
something to become different so I'm
有些事情变得与众不同，所以我
gonna get the first guy to move B from
会得到第一个将B从
the bottom to the top and I'm gonna look
从下到上，我要看
at what happens here if nothing changes
如果什么都没有改变这里会发生什么
I'm gonna add the second guy do it I'm
我要加第二个人做
gonna keep working my way through until
要继续努力直到
at some point B moves move somewhere
在某个时候B移动到某处
something different happens and then I'm
发生了一些不同的事情，然后我
gonna say alright I found my end star
会说好吧，我找到了我的终极明星
that guy who made a difference is then
那位有所作为的人是
star so so now let me give some names to
星，所以现在让我给
preference orderings because I need them
偏好顺序，因为我需要它们
for the rest of the proof so I'm gonna
对于其余的证明，我要
denote by pref one the profile just
用pref一表示档案
before n star moves B and I'm going to
在n星移动B之前，我要
denote by pres to the profile just after
由个人资料之前的个人资料表示
n star has moved B to the top and let's
n星将B移到顶部，让我们
note that in pref one we have B at the
请注意，在首选中，我们在
bottom in the social welfare order in so
在社会福利秩序的底部
our social Authority here is B at the
我们的社会权威在这里是B
bottom and in pref to B is is in some
在B的最下面并且在某些位置
different place than it was before and
与以前不同的地方
every voter ranks be at either the top
每个选民名列前茅
or at the bottom right so so notice here
或在右下角，所以请注意这里
we have B's at the top for everybody
每个人的顶部都有B
here we have B's at the bottom for
在这里，我们在底部有B
everybody and here again we have these
大家，这里又有这些
at the top and B's at the bottom but
在顶部，B在底部，但是
what's changed is NSTAR so here's the
更改的是NSTAR，所以这是
one guy who's actually moved something
一个真正动了东西的家伙
and by our argument in step one
根据第一步的论证
both of these profiles have be in
这两个配置文件都在
extremal positions and so it must be
极端的位置，所以它必须是
that the social welfare function also
社会福利功能也
puts be in an extremal position and
放在极端位置
because we've defined on star as the
因为我们已经将star定义为
person who causes B to change it must
导致B更改它的人必须
therefore be in this profile press two
因此在此配置文件中按两次
that B is at the top and I noticed that
B在顶部，我注意到
that means now that we've proven the
这意味着现在我们已经证明了
thing we set out to prove there exists
我们开始证明存在的事物
some voter who is able to change his
一些能够改变他的选民
vote at some profile at this profile in
在此个人资料中对某个人资料进行投票
order to move some outcome B from the
为了从
bottom to the top okay let's get to step
从底部到顶部好吧，让我们开始
three so now I want a reason about this
三个，所以我现在想要一个原因
same guy n star
同一个男星
so recall n star has special power over
所以记得n星具有特殊的力量
outcome B in this very narrow way that
结果B以这种非常狭窄的方式
there's there exists this one special
那里有这个特别
profile that we constructed pref one
我们构建的配置文件之一
where he can move B from the bottom to
他可以将B从底部移动到
the top well now I want to reason about
现在我想推理一下
this same guy and I want to claim
这个家伙，我想主张
something that all of a sudden seems
突然之间似乎有些东西
very strong but he's a dictator over any
非常坚强，但他是独裁者
pair AC that doesn't involve B what does
对不涉及B的AC做些什么
that mean it means that the social
这意味着它意味着社会
welfare function must make every
福利功能必须使每个
decision between any pair AC where I'm
我在任何一对AC之间的决定
using those variable names just to
使用这些变量名只是为了
denote anything that isn't B simply by
仅仅表示不是B的任何东西
listening to what n star thinks so if n
听n星的想法，如果n
star like C better than a the social
像C的明星胜过社交
welfare function will as well and it
福利功能也会
just doesn't matter what anybody else
别人没关系
thinks so that's what we want to claim
认为这就是我们要主张的
here so how does this argument work well
在这里，这个论点如何运作良好
so we're gonna begin by by choosing one
所以我们首先要选择一个
of the two elements from the pair and
该对中两个元素中的一个
let's call the one that we choose a so
我们称其为“选择一个”
now I'm gonna construct a new preference
现在我要建立一个新的偏好
profile pref 3 which differs from pref 2
配置文件pref 3与pref 2不同
in two ways first of all I'm going to
首先要以两种方式
move a to the very top of n stars
将a移至n个星的最高点
preference ordering leaving everything
优先订购留下一切
else unchanged so I'm going to take a
否则保持不变，所以我将采取
wherever it was here and I'm gonna move
无论在哪里，我都会搬家
it up to the top you'll notice by the
它到达顶部，您会注意到
way in these pictures if you can read it
如果您可以阅读这些图片中的方式
some of the variable names are bald and
一些变量名是秃头的，
some of the variable names are not bald
一些变量名不是秃头的
the ones that are bold are things we've
那些大胆的是我们所拥有的
made explicit assumptions about and the
对和做明确的假设。
things that are not bald are given for
不秃顶的东西是给的
illustrations but we haven't actually
插图，但实际上我们还没有
assumed so if you can make it out you'll
假设如此，如果您能做到，您将
see here a is not bold because we
看到这里a不大胆，因为我们
haven't assumed anything about where it
并没有假设任何有关它的地方
goes and over here a becomes bold
过去，在这里变得大胆
because now we've assumed that it goes
因为现在我们假设它会
to the top of n stars or during all
到n颗星的顶部或全部
right so so anyway we're making two
对，所以无论如何我们要做两个
changes so our first change is to move a
变化，所以我们的第一个变化是移动
to the top and then star is ordering and
到顶部，然后星级正在排序，
that means that for n star a is most
这意味着对于n星来说，a是最大的
preferred and a is preferred to B which
首选，而a优于B，其中
is preferred to C because a and B are
比C更可取，因为a和B是
both of the top so wherever C is it must
两者都这样，所以无论在哪里C
be further death and second we're just
再进一步死亡，第二，我们只是
gonna arbitrarily scramble the relative
会任意争夺亲戚
rankings of a and C for all voters other
所有其他选民的a和C排名
than n star without changing the
比n星不变
position of B which is always extremal
B的位置始终是极值
so we're just gonna kind of move around
所以我们只是要四处走动
a and C and some kind of arbitrary way
a和C以及某种任意方式
but we're gonna make sure that we still
但我们要确保我们仍然
leave be in the same place for everybody
每个人都留在同一个地方
else that it always was
否则，它总是
alright so that that's our preference
好，那是我们的偏爱
profile prep 3 now notice that in
个人资料准备3现在注意到
preference profile pref 1 we had that a
偏好设定档偏好1，
was preferred socially to B and the
在社交方面优于B，
reason we can conclude that is that we
我们可以得出结论的原因是，我们
know that B was actually at the very
知道B实际上在
bottom of the social order
社会秩序的底部
so everything was preferred to B and so
所以一切都比B好，所以
a in particular must have been preferred
特别是一定是首选
to B now when we compare pref 1 to prep
现在，当我们比较首选项1和准备
3 the relative rankings between a and B
3 a和B之间的相对排名
are the same for everybody because B is
每个人都一样，因为B是
in the same extrema position for
在相同的极值位置
everybody except for n star who moves B
除了n星移动B
but we've we've then changed it to put a
但是我们已经将其更改为
above B and so it's the case that these
在B上方，因此情况是
guys over here have be above a in both
在这两个家伙都高于
cases these guys have a above B in both
如果这些家伙在两个人中都高于B
cases and M star also has a above
案例和M星也有一个上面
be in both cases because here we
在这两种情况下都可以，因为在这里
actually moved a to be above B so from
实际上将a移到了B之上，所以从
this fact we can conclude that in prep 3
这个事实我们可以得出结论，在准备3中
it must be that a gets socially
一定是社交
preferred to B because by independence
优先于B，因为具有独立性
of irrelevant alternatives the social
不相关的替代方案
choice between a and B can only depend
a和B之间的选择只能取决于
on their relative rankings by the
他们的相对排名
different agents and we've just seen
不同的代理商，我们刚刚看到
those relative rankings are the same in
这些相对排名在
pref 1 and in prep 3 now we're going to
Pref 1和Prep 3现在我们要
say something similar comparing pref 2
说类似的东西比较首选项2
and prep 3 so in pref 2 we had the B was
和prep 3，所以在pref 2中，我们的B是
socially preferred to C because we know
在社会上优于C，因为我们知道
that improv to be was at the very top of
即兴发挥是最重要的
the social ordering and so wherever C
社会秩序等等C
was it was somewhere further down and in
在更远的地方吗？
a similar way to as what we argued
与我们争论的方式类似
before the relative rankings between B
在B之间的相对排名之前
and C are the same in pref 2 and prep 3
和C在pref 2和prep 3中相同
let's see why that is so we have for all
让我们看看为什么会这样，我们所有人
the agents other than End star B is in
末星B以外的特工在
the same extremal position in both cases
在两种情况下相同的末梢位置
so wherever C is its ordering must be
所以无论C的顺序是什么
the same and for n star things are a
和n星一样
little bit different and star used to
有点不同，星过去
have B in the very top position here and
在这里B处于最高位置
here he has ends to a B in the second
在第二个他已经结束
position
位置
but the thing above it is a so in both
但上面的东西在两个方面都是这样
cases where ever see is it's somewhere
曾经见过的地方
downstream and so again we see that B
下游，所以我们再次看到B
because the relative rankings are the
因为相对排名是
same in both places it must be that the
在两个地方都一样，一定是
social ordering again is the same so
社会秩序再次是一样的
here we had that the social ordering
在这里，我们有社会秩序
says B is higher up than C and so here
说B比C高，所以这里
it must also be could be as high Repton
它一定也可以和雷普顿一样高
see in the social welfare ranking so
在社会福利排名中看到
using these two facts that we've just
利用我们刚才提到的两个事实
established and transitivity we can draw
建立和传递性
the conclusion that the social welfare
社会福利的结论
ordering must give us that a is bigger
订购必须给我们一个更大的
is preferred to see in prep 3 ok why do
最好在准备3中看到，确定为什么
we care about that well let's construct
我们关心的很好，让我们构建
more preference profile I promise this
更多的个人资料，我保证
is the last one prep for by changing
是改变的最后一个准备
prep three in two ways first of all
首先以两种方式准备三个
let's arbitrarily change the position of
让我们随意改变位置
B in every voters ordering while keeping
每位选民中的B在保持的同时
all of the other relative preferences
所有其他相对偏好
the same so we're going from prep 3 to
一样，所以我们从准备3到
prep for by taking B and just kind of
拿B做些准备
sticking it somewhere else and but we're
贴在其他地方，但是我们
not going to move around any of the
不会四处走动
other relative or preference orderings
其他相对或优先顺序
secondly we're going to move a to an
其次，我们将移动到
arbitrary position in n stars ordering
n星排序中的任意位置
with a constraint that a is kept higher
约束a保持较高
than C so let's look at that so here we
比C好，让我们来看一下
have a in a really special place here
在一个非常特别的地方
we're just gonna stick it further down
我们只是将其进一步压低
to here but we're gonna make sure that
到这里，但我们要确保
it's still higher than where C is and
它仍然比C高
what I want you to observe now is that
我要你现在观察的是
all voters other than n star at this
除了n星以外的所有选民
point have completely arbitrary
点完全是任意的
preferences because the only things that
偏好，因为只有
we had assumed about those voters ever
我们曾经假设过那些选民
before was the position of the B's right
乙的权利的位置之前
those are the only things that we had
那是我们唯一拥有的东西
bold in those figures because that's all
这些数字中的粗体是因为仅此而已
we assumed all this other stuff here
我们在这里假设了所有其他东西
it's just completely arbitrary
这是完全任意的
furthermore n star also has arbitrary
此外，n星也具有任意性
preferences except for the fact that a
偏好，但以下事实除外
is is preferred by n star to C now what
现在n星比C更喜欢
do we do with prep for well in prep
我们会做好准备吗？
three and prep for all of the agents
三，为所有代理做准备
have the same relative preferences
具有相同的相对偏好
between a and C right so we've moved
在A和C之间，所以我们已经移动了
things all around but we've done it in a
周围的一切，但我们已经做到了
way that still has all of the agents in
仍然有所有代理商的方式
3 & 4 having the same preferences
3和4具有相同的首选项
between a and C and that and we know
在a和C之间，并且我们知道
that in prep 3 the social welfare
在准备3中，社会福利
function has to rank a higher than C so
函数必须比C高
by independence of irrelevant
通过无关的独立性
alternatives in
替代品
must be that the welfare function also
必须是福利功能
ranks say above C and prep for but
排名高于C并为此做好准备
that's pretty interesting because the
这很有趣，因为
only thing we've assumed about prep for
我们假设只有准备
is that a goes above c4 and start and
是a超过c4然后开始
that means that we've established that
这意味着我们已经确定
then we wanted to establish which is
然后我们想确定哪个是
that n star is all by himself able to
n星本身就可以
determine the relative ranking between a
确定一个之间的相对排名
and C regardless of what everybody else
和C不管其他人
says so that makes them a dictator over
这样说，使他们成为独裁者
the pair AC well clearly I'm gonna want
这对交流很好，我想要
eventually to say n star is a dictator
最终说n星是独裁者
over everything not just over AC but
不仅可以通过交流，还可以通过一切
also over pairs a B pairs that do
也超过一对B对
involve B so this turns out actually to
涉及到B，所以事实证明
be very easy to show so let's consider
很容易显示，所以让我们考虑
some third outcome C so I'm claiming now
一些第三结果C，所以我现在声明
that n star as the dictator over pairs a
那个n星作为双子的独裁者a
B so let me think about some third
B，让我想想第三点
outcome C well by the argument that I
我认为我的结果很好
already made in step two there's some
已经在第二步中做了一些
voter let's call him and double star
选民叫他和双星
who's extremely pivotal for C right so I
对C至关重要的人，所以我
can make that same argument that I made
可以提出与我相同的论点
before where C starts out at the bottom
在C从底部开始之前
for everyone and the social ordering has
为每个人和社会秩序
it at the bottom and then I started
它在底部，然后我开始
moving things to the top until something
把东西移到顶部
changes I'm eventually I can see that it
变化，最终我可以看到
changes there and whoever the guy is who
在那里改变，不管那个人是谁
made a change let's call that a double
进行了更改，我们称其为双倍
star and in principle maybe this is a
明星，原则上也许这是一个
different guy there's nothing in step
不同的家伙没有什么可分的
two that says it has to be the same
两个说必须相同
person it just says there's nothing
人，它只是说什么都没有
special about beat it made it the thing
关于击败的特殊之处使其成为现实
that had to move around it would have
那必须四处走动
worked for anything so it worked for
为任何东西工作，所以它为
example for C well now I can use the
C的例子，现在我可以使用
argument in step three to say that this
第三步的论点是说
guy that we've just identified and
我们刚刚确定的那个人，
double star is a dictator over any pair
双星是任何一对的独裁者
alpha beta which doesn't involve C right
不涉及C权利的alpha beta
I'm just basically running through the
我基本上只是在经历
arguments I had before but renaming the
我之前有过争论，但重命名了
variables so of course a B is an example
变量，所以当然B是一个例子
of such a pair alpha beta right so so by
对这样的alpha beta，所以
this argument there's somebody who's a
这个论点有人
dictator over over the pair a B so what
一对B的独裁者怎么办
I want to show is that that person is n
我想证明的是那个人是n
star you know you I might worry that
明星你知道你我可能会担心
there are different dictators for
有不同的独裁者
and things but notice that I've already
和其他事情，但是请注意，我已经
observed that n star is able to affect
观察到n星能够影响
the way that W relatively ranks a and B
W相对排名a和B的方式
for example we saw this in the movement
例如我们在运动中看到了
from the profile pref one two pref two
从个人资料偏好一二偏好二
right when we had this profile where B
对，当我们拥有此配置文件时，B
was at the bottom whoops I'm doing that
在底部，我正在这么做
wrong let me do it again we had this
不对，让我再做一次
ranking where B was at the top for a
排名B在a的顶部
couple people is at the bottom for end
夫妻是最后的结局
star it was at the bottom for other
明星，这是在其他人的底部
people and then we move it up to the top
人，然后我们将其移至顶部
we saw that that caused the social
我们看到这导致了社会
welfare ordering to take B and move it
福利命令取B并将其移动
from the bottom to the top and that
从底部到顶部
means that n star is able to affect the
表示n星能够影响
relative ranking between a and B because
A和B之间的相对排名，因为
wherever a is it's somewhere in the
无论它在哪里
middle here in the social ordering and
在社会秩序中间
so the relative ranking between a and B
所以a和B之间的相对排名
got affected by what and starred
受什么影响并出演了
declared goodbye this change that only n
宣布再见，只有n
star made and what I've now just argued
明星造的，我现在刚刚争论过的
is that there has to be some dictator
是必须有一些独裁者
over a B pairs and so if n star was able
超过B对，所以如果n星能够
to make any difference to a B pairs he
对B对有什么影响
has to be that dictator because it's not
必须是那个独裁者，因为它不是
possible to have both a dictator for a B
可能同时拥有B的独裁者
pairs and a different person whoever
对和另一个人
makes a difference to the a B ranking
使A B排名有所不同
and so that means that this n double
所以这意味着这n倍
star and M star must be the same agent
星和M星必须是同一代理
and that means n star is a dictator over
这意味着n星是独裁者
everything and start is just a full
一切都开始了
dictator and that means no matter what
独裁者，那就意味着无论如何
social welfare function I have if it's
我有的社会福利功能
Pareto efficient and if it's independent
帕累托高效且独立
of irrelevant alternatives it has to be
不相关的选择
some dictatorial Social Welfare function
一些独裁的社会福利职能
which means the only freedom you have in
这意味着您拥有的唯一自由
such a social welfare function is the
这样的社会福利功能是
freedom to decide which person is the
自由决定哪个人是
dictator and if you have any other
独裁者，如果还有其他
social welfare function which isn't
社会福利功能不是
dictatorial then it must be that it's
独裁的话那一定是
either not preeto efficient or it's not
要么效率不高，要么效率不高
independent of irrelevant alternatives
独立于无关的选择
and that explains why we have voting
这就解释了为什么我们要投票
systems that cause things like the
导致诸如
number of votes that Ralph Nader gets
拉尔夫·纳德（Ralph Nader）获得的票数
effect who wins the election in Florida
谁赢得佛罗里达大选的影响
that's a case of not being independent
那是不独立的情况
of irrelevant alternatives and that's
不相关的替代方案，那就是
usually the the axiom that we relaxed
通常我们放松的公理
because not being pre to efficient would
因为不追求效率会
be really terrible
真的很糟糕
that means if everybody all agrees about
这意味着如果所有人都同意
something sometimes the social welfare
有时是社会福利
function would do something different
函数会做一些不同的事情
anyway that's something that we're
无论如何，这就是我们
usually not willing to tolerate and so
通常不愿意容忍等等
the practical consequence of Eros
爱神的实际后果
theorem is that we end up having social
定理是，我们最终有社会
welfare functions that are not
不是的福利功能
independent of irrelevant alternatives
独立于无关的选择